Crone, Michelle; Papers apap101
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Audio, 1979-1995, Undated; 7; 1.25 cubic ft.
  - Judith Sloan - The Whole K'Cufin' World…and a few more things, 1992 (Cassette 149)
  - Fred Small, Undated (Cassette 150)
  - Smith and Bakken - feel so alive, 1992 (Cassette 151)
  - The Snickering Witches - First Tellings, 1992 (Cassette 152)
  - Southern Festival Mediation, Undated (Cassette 153)
  - Southern Festival Mediation, Undated (Cassette 154)
  - Elinore Speeks - Eastern Girl, 1994 (Cd 11)
  - Spinning Wheel - Living Breathing, 1992 (Cassette 155)
  - St. T- Street Preacher, Undated (Cassette 156)
  - Doug Stevens and the Outband, 1992 (Cassette 157)
  - Suede - Barely Blue, Undated (Cassette 158)
  - Suffragettes, Undated (Cassette 159)
  - Barbara Lee Supeno - Slow Down, 1993 (Cassette 160)
  - Uzume Taiko - Chiroshi, 1990 (Cassette 161)
  - Marcia Taylor - Love Every Step of the Way, 1987 (Cassette 162)
  - T- Bone Sphinx, Undated (Cassette 163)
  - This Way Out, Undated (Cassette 164)
  - Jo Thomas, 1988 (Cassette 165)
  - Jan Tilley, Undated (Cassette 166)
  - Julia Tipton - Live at the Mean Fiddler, 1993 (Cassette 167)
  - Together, Proud, and Strong, 1993 (Cassette 168)
  - Elaine Townsend - Heartbreaker Blues, 1989 (Cassette 169)
  - Toxic Marys, Undated (Cassette 170)
  - Lisa Travis - From Scratch, 1988 (Cassette 171)
  - Triphoria, 1993 (Cassette 172)
  - Triviatas - Fern Draussen Im Dunkel, 1991 (Cassette 173)
  - Nancy Tucker, 1987 (Cassette 174)
  - Two Nice Girls - Like a version, 1990 (Cassette 175)
  - Two of Hearts - Shout it out!, 1991 (Cassette 176)
  - Two of Hearts - Shout it out!, 1991 (Cassette 177)
  - Judy Valenti - Touch Me, 1993 (Cassette 178)
  - Various Artists - A Little Nip, 1994 (Cd 12)
  - Venus Envy - I'll be a homo for Christmas, Undated (Cassette 179)
  - Venus Envy - Unarmed and dangerous, 1990 (Cassette 180)
  - Kathryn Warner, 1992 (Cassette 181)
  - WBAI Studio Recording, Undated (Cassette 182)
  - Tom Wilson Weinberg - Don't mess with mary, 1994 (Cassette 183)
  - Tom Wilson Weinberg - Get used to it!, 1993 (Cassette 184)
  - Tom Wilson Weinberg - Ten Percent Revue, 1987 (Cassette 185)
  - Sam Weis, 1990 (Cassette 186)
  - Lorrie Wesoly and Night Vision, Undated (Cassette 187)
  - Laura Wetzler - Jesse Helms has made a radical out of me, 1990 (Cassette 188)
  - Laura Wetzler - A World of Jewish Folk Music, 1992 (Cassette 189)
  - Erica Wheeler, Undated (Cassette 190)
  - The Wild Hearts, 1991 (Cassette 191)
  - Winkte and crazy sacred dogs, 1991 (Cassette 192)
  - Winkte and crazy sacred dogs, Undated (Cassette 193)
  - Roz Winter - No Hiding, 1993 (Cassette 194)
  - Julie Wolf Quartet, Undated (Cassette 195)
  - Kate Wolf, Undated (Cassette 196)
  - Work - Plantet Earth, Undated (Cassette 197)
  - The Wyrd Sisters - Leave a Little Light, 1992 (Cassette 198)
  - Xscape - Tonight, 1994 (Cassette 199)
  - Yagottawanna - Don't Stop, 1992 (Cassette 200)
  - Yagottawanna - Live!, 1993 (Cassette 201)
  - Yagottawanna - Sampler, Undated (Cassette 202)
  - Yer Girlfriend - We Won't Be Silent, 1989 (Cassette 203)
- Video, 1989-1994, Undated; 8; 3.3 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical by performer or title.
  This series consists of unassociated VHS tapes and one Umatic tape. Many of these items are demos used by Michelle Crone to select performers for the various festivals and events she organized.
  - Adult Children of Heterosexuals, Undated (Vhs 21)
  - Ain't Helen, 1993 (Vhs 22)
  - And we fall in love, Undated (Vhs 23)
  - Frank Aqueno - Queer Pier, 1992 (Vhs 24)
  - Tom Aramiano, Undated (Vhs 25)
  - Asian AIDS Project, Undated (Vhs 26)
  - Axis Dance Troupe - Helix, 1992 (Vhs 27)
  - B-Average, Undated (Vhs 28)
  - Hank Baron - Original Songs, 1993 (Vhs 29)
  - Amanda Bearse - PSA National Coming Out Day, Undated (Vhs 30)
  - Ronit Bezalel - Shirley and Florence, Undated (Vhs 31)
  - Blackberri - Demo, Undated (Vhs 32)
  - Erika Block - The Song of the Lark, Undated (Vhs 33)
  - Amy Boyd - Demo, Undated (Vhs 34)
  - M. Brownsey, Undated (Vhs 35)
  - Maureen Brownsey, Undated (Vhs 36)
  - Rick Burd, Undated (Vhs 37)
  - Camp Winding Gap, Undated (Vhs 38)
  - Seraiah Carol, 1992 (Vhs 39)
  - Seraiah Carol Live! "Do Ya Wanna Funk" 1993 March on Washington Main Stage Rally (Vhs 40)
  - Seraiah Carol Live! "Do Ya Wanna Funk" 1993 March on Washington Main Stage Rally (Vhs 41)
  - Maggie Cassella, 1992 (Vhs 42)
  - Cell33, 1992 (Vhs 43)
  - Choose Agenda - Interviews, 1989 (Vhs 44)
  - Chris Cinque - The Shrub, Undated (Vhs 45)
  - The Church Ladies for Choice - In your face with Amazing Grace, 1993 (Vhs 46)
  - Fruit Cocktail, 1993 (Vhs 47)
  - Sara Cytron, 1990 (Vhs 48)
  - Julia Dares, 1993 (Vhs 49)
  - Lea DeLaria - In the Life, 1993 (Vhs 50)
  - Michael Red Earth - Shades, 1993 (Vhs 51)
  - Chrisanne Eastwood, Undated (Vhs 52)
  - The Flirtations - In the Life, Undated (Vhs 53)
  - Friday, Undated (Vhs 54)
  - Kurt Fulton - Sodomite Warriors, 1989 (Vhs 55)
  - Lisa Geduldig - Selected Comedy Performances, Undated (Vhs 56)
  - Judy Gold, 1993 (Vhs 57)
  - Sharon Gonzalez - Bi the Way - A look at the Bisexual Community, Undated (Umatic 1)
  - Monica Grant, Undated (Vhs 58)
  - Sorrel Hays - C.D., The Ritual of Civil Disobedience, Undated (Vhs 59)
  - Jerry Halliday and His Big Bad Broads, Undated (Vhs 60)
  - Susan Herrick, Undated (Vhs 61)
  - Reed Hortie - Performs Andrew Dile Gay, 1993 (Vhs 62)
  - Reijhugu Horumawzu, Undated (Vhs 63)
  - Island of Souls Productions featuring Onyx, 1993 (Vhs 64)
  - Kaleidoscope Theatre Co. - Women: Images and Impressions (Part 1), Undated (Vhs 65)
  - Pam Kansas, Undated (Vhs 66)
  - Andrew Kelm - Black Bride, 1994 (Vhs 67)
  - Tracy Kennedy - Unplugged, Undated (Vhs 68)
  - The Killer Condom, Undated (Vhs 69)
  - Elvira Kurt - All Gay Material, Undated (Vhs 70)
  - Elvira Kurt - Straight and Gay Material, Undated (Vhs 71)
  - David Lamble - Mihe's Film, 1993 (Vhs 72)
  - David Lamble - Mihe's Film/Bashing, 1990 (Vhs 73)
  - Eva Lang, Undated (Vhs 74)
  - Lavender Light Gospel Choir, 1993 (Vhs 75)
  - Life and Times of Harvey Milk, Undated (Vhs 76)
  - Liz, Undated (Vhs 77)
  - Marla BB and her Sassy Mama Blues Band, Undated (Vhs 78)
  - Shelly Mars - Sample Tape, Undated (Vhs 79)
  - Sabrina Matthews, Undated (Vhs 80)
  - John McGivern - Med-West Side Story, Undated (Vhs 81)
  - Mimi - Freed, 1992 (Vhs 82)
  - Lynda Montgomery, Undated (Vhs 83)
  - Mary F. Morton and Natalie R. Hutchinson - The NIA Project, Undated (Vhs 84)
  - The Nellie Oleson's, Undated (Vhs 85)
  - Oh So Politically Correct Players - 21st Century Party Performance, 1992 (Vhs 86)
  - Stephen Patterson - All About Steve, 1993 (Vhs 87)
  - Janice Perry - Queen Lear, 1993 (Vhs 88)
  - Georgia Ragsdale, Undated (Vhs 89)
  - Sandy Rapp - A Concert for Now, Undated (Vhs 90)
  - Ernie Real and the Real Appeal, 1992 (Vhs 91)
  - Karen Ripley - Headliner, 1992 (Vhs 92)
  - Brigitte E.M. Rondeau - Sister Dyke-Auto-Me, Undated (Vhs 93)
  - Tracy Rose - Demo, Undated (Vhs 94)
  - Chuck Roy, Undated (Vhs 95)
  - Sacarley - Entertainment Conference LAC, Undated (Vhs 96)
  - Eugene Salandra - Animation Sample Reel, Undated (Vhs 97)
  - Eugene Salandra - Faerie Film, 1993 (Vhs 98)
  - Bob Smith, 1993 (Vhs 99)
  - Sounds of St. Croix, Undated (Vhs 100)
  - Spinning Wheel, Undated (Vhs 101)
  - Straight from the Heart, Undated (Vhs 102)
  - Jason Stuart - Stand-up Live, Undated (Vhs 103)
  - Lynn Thomas, Undated (Vhs 104)
  - Lynn Thomas, 1992 (Vhs 105)
  - Timepiece, Undated (Vhs 106)
  - Two-Spirited/Thunder People, Undated (Vhs 107)
  - Oliver Wadsworth - Struggles in Daddy's Dress, Undated (Vhs 108)
  - Marcia Wilkie - This Girl I Knew, Undated (Vhs 109)
  - Danny Williams, 1994 (Vhs 110)
  - Roz Winter, 1993 (Vhs 111)